Aleena Aqeel

07306240409 aleena-a@hotmail.com

Skills Summary

Proficient and creative developer with strong experience in website management and development. Efficient in all aspects of web design and development including WordPress sites with experience in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Python, JavaScript, and PHP. Skilled in creating engaging and interactive websites. Excel at time-management, have good communication skills, can work independently as well as in a team.

Work Experience

FullSphere April 2022 – Present **Junior Web Developer**

- Developed accessible and responsive sites using HTML, CSS and JavaScript for clients
- Manage and maintain the company site by updating the website regularly with new work projects
- Run and manage email campaigns using CRM Platform
- Developed HTML Newsletters for email campaigns which increased client engagement
- Learned how to use Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign

Nat's Wholesale Ltd Oct 2021 - March 2022

WordPress Developer

Developed an e-commerce website for the client. The wireframes were designed using Figma and the website was developed using WordPress, WooCommerce, HTML and CSS. My role inlcuded managing the social media campaign and handling the SEO of the site by creating content to drive traffic using tools like Cloudflare, Google Analytics, Google search console and plugins like All-in-one SEO.

Education

University of Manchester Sept 2020 – Sept 2021

MSc ACS: Software Engineering

Manchester Metropolitan University Sept 2017 – July 2020

BSc Web Development